He never knew what hit him.
Secret Admirer is a comedy, romance film directed by David Greenwalt.
An anonymous love letter left in Michael Ryan's locker on the last day of school wreaks
havoc on his life and the lives of everyone who comes in contact with it.
Michael Ryan, played by C. Thomas Howell.
Toni, played by Lori Loughlin.
Deborah Anne Fimple, played by Kelly Preston.
Connie Ryan, played by Dee Wallace.
George Ryan, played by Cliff DeYoung.
Elizabeth Fimple, played by Leigh Taylor-Young.
Secret Admirer is a 1985 American teen romantic comedy film co-written and directed by
David Greenwalt in his feature film directorial debut, and starring C.
Thomas Howell, Lori Loughlin, Kelly Preston and Fred Ward.
The original music score was composed by Jan Hammer.
The film was produced at the height of the teen sex
comedy cinema craze in the mid-1980s.
The film explores themes of love letter, summer, summer
vacation, teen comedy, secret admirer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.